People have served your content based on
the algorithm.
They're not going to look for it. I
was like,
if you can make a piece of content,
there'll be eight videos in front of them,
they pick yours, that's the real
flex.
Mm.
And also, I came to realize that
when a subject is really important to me
I will find a YouTube video,
and I'll actually put the phone down as
I'm listening.
Mm.
So
trying to distinguish between getting the
Audi RS4 or the Audi RS6
it's an 18-minute video.
After the first minute,
my shoulders relax,
I put it on the side,
I start emptying the dishwasher,
and I listen.
Mm.
That way of communicating with people,
I think, is so
elite and almost 1,000 views in that
way is more valuable than 50,000 views on
a short or a
reel. And for me, I was like,
I want to have an emotional connection
with
someone that goes beyond just the funny
reel or 60 seconds.
Mm.
But I still need to keep catering to the
people that don't fucking want to listen
10 minutes.